tanoshiijapanese.com 2017-07-16

# Privacy Policy - Tanoshii Japanese

\- Updated April 2012

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the www.tanoshiijapanese.com website.

There are many aspects of this site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to some features you are required to submit some personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username, password and email address. Other optional personally identifable information may be collected and used for the purpose of enhancing your website experience. Where practical, the purpose for which we are collecting this personal information will be made clear at the time of collection. Please be aware that when you voluntarily post personal information into a comment, review, article or forum post, that information will not be protected by this privacy policy.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may be required to release your information where required by Australian law.

For each visitor who accesses the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to the ip address, browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

www.tanoshiijapanese.com reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this site.

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing. www.tanoshiijapanese.com reserves the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis.

www.tanoshiijapanese.com welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us using the contact form.
